<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<strings>
	<string name="help">Help</string>
	<string name="plants">Plants</string>
	<string name="topics">Topics</string>
	<string name="general">General</string>
	<string name="advanced_topics">Advanced Topics</string>
	<string name="wild_animals">Wild Animals</string>
	<string name="see_also">See Also</string>
	<string name="entities">Entities</string>
	<string name="requirements">Requirements</string>
	<string name="loading_hints">Hints</string>
	<string name="help_upgrades">Upgrades</string>
	<string name="defense">Defense</string>
	<string name="help_stats">Stats</string>
	<string name="help_cost">Costs</string>
	<string name="help_main">Main Topic</string>
	<string name="help_categories">Categories</string>
	<string name="help_recurrent_production">Recurrent Production</string>
	<string name="help_related_resources">Related Resources</string>
	<string name="help_production">Resources Produced</string>
	<string name="help_byproducts">Resources Produced</string>
	<string name="help_domestic_variant">Domestic Variant</string>
	<string name="help_wild_variant">Wild Variant</string>
	<string name="help_domestication_tech">Domestication Tech</string>
	<string name="help_crafted_from">Crafted from</string>
	<string name="help_built_using">Built using</string>	
	<string name="help_produced_from">Produced from</string>
	<string name="help_created_entities">Used to create</string>
	<string name="help_produced_resources">Produced Resources</string>
	<string name="help_input_resources">Used Resources</string>

	<string name="hint_0">Gather (b)Berries(/b) and (b)Fruit(/b) during summer and save longer lasting resources such as (b)Cured Meat(/b), (b)Dry Fish(/b), and (b)Grain(/b) for winter.</string>
	<string name="hint_1">(b)Avoid(/b) targeting (b)healthy adult(/b) animals when hunting in the (b)early game(/b), as they are hard to kill and might fight back.</string>
	<string name="hint_2">Use (b)work areas(/b) in conjunction with (b)resource limits(/b) to automate your settlement as much as possible.</string>
	<string name="hint_3">Don't (b)expand(/b) too fast if you don't have the (b)infrastructure(/b) to feed your people.</string>
	<string name="hint_4">(b)Domestic animals(/b) need to be (b)fed(/b) and given (b)water(/b) in (b)winter(/b). Avoid having too many if you can not maintain them.</string>
	<string name="hint_5">In (b)paleolithic(/b) hunter-gatherer societies, (b)conflict(/b) was (b)rare(/b), as the human populations were sparse. From the (b)neolithic onward(/b), though, you really need to be prepared for (b)battle(/b).</string>
	<string name="hint_6">It's (b)hard(/b) to achieve (b)large populations(/b) in the (b)early(/b) eras. Only with farming and other technologies will you be able to sustain a large settlement.</string>
	<string name="hint_7">Make sure that when (b)winter(/b) comes you have plenty of (b)non perishable food(/b) in storage, otherwise starvation will be a serious problem.</string>
	<string name="hint_8">Getting someone to go to rivers, lakes, or wells to (b)collect and store water(/b) is way more (b)efficient(/b) than having your people go drink away from the settlement every time.</string>
	<string name="hint_9">You can (b)customize(/b) the panels at the top of the screen by clicking on the (b)+(/b) buttons next to them.</string>	
	<string name="hint_10">(b)Pivot the camera(/b) around a point by pressing both (b)pan(/b) and (b)rotate(/b) keys at the same time.</string>
	<string name="hint_11">In (b)standard(/b) difficulty, raider (b)technology(/b) will (b)match(/b) your current era, so be careful before advancing too quickly.</string>
	<string name="hint_12">In (b)hardcore(/b) difficulty, attackers will advance their (b)technology(/b) at their (b)own pace(/b), so you should not take too long to progress through the eras.</string>
	<string name="hint_13">You can tell your people to go (b)rest(/b) or (b)shelter(/b) by selecting them and (b)right clicking(/b) on a (b)structure(/b).</string>
	<string name="hint_14">When people get (b)hurt(/b) there is a chance they might catch an (b)infection(/b), which could be fatal.</string>
	<string name="hint_15">You can give (b)commands(/b) to your people by (b)selecting(/b) them and (b)right clicking(/b) on the terrain or on an object.</string>
	<string name="hint_16">You can (b)command(/b) your people to (b)sprint(/b) to a location by selecting them and (b)double right clicking(/b) on the terrain.</string>
	<string name="hint_17">You can (b)quicksave(/b) the game by pressing (b)F9(/b).</string>
	<string name="hint_18">(b)Double click(/b) on a plant, being or building to select all similar (b)nearby entities(/b).</string>
	<string name="hint_19">You can press the (camera_center_town_key) key to move the camera back to town.</string>
	<string name="hint_20">You can hold the (hunter_selection_key) and (fighter_selection_key) keys while dragging the mouse to select people with (b)hunting(/b) or (b)fighting(/b) tools only.</string>
	<string name="hint_21">You can use (b)primal vision(/b) mode to highlight (b)work areas(/b).</string>


	<string name="help_main_title">Dawn of Man</string>
	<string name="help_main_description">
In (b)Dawn of Man(/b) you guide a settlement of ancient humans in their struggle for survival.
You will have to (b)hunt(/b), (b)gather(/b), (b)craft tools(/b), (b)fight(/b), research new (b)techs(/b) and face the challenges the environment will throw at you.
</string>

  <!-- === Topics === -->

	<string name="help_hunting_title">Hunting</string>
	<string name="help_hunting_description">
Using specialized tools, your people can hunt animals in order to obtain (b)food(/b) and (b)resources(/b) from them.
To start a hunt, select an animal in the environment and then click on the (b)hunt button(/b). Depending on the difficulty of the prey, and the availability of tools, a certain number of people will go after the animal.
Animals will react in different ways when being hunted: some will try to (b)escape(/b), others will protect their offspring or will try to (b)retaliate(/b).
You can control the hunt in more detail by selecting one or more adults and right clicking on a target animal.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_farming_title">Farming</string>
	<string name="help_farming_description">
Farming allows you to automate the production of (b)food(/b), and sustain more people in your settlement.
You can plant a variety of (b)crops(/b), then harvest and process them to feed your people. Crops are usually planted in winter or spring and collected in summer or autumn.
It is important to plant a (b)variety(/b) of crops as diseases can easily wipe out all the individuals of a single species.
In order to maximize the efficiency of the harvest, make sure you have enough (b)Sickles(/b) around.
Of all crops, (b)cereals(/b) are probably the most important, they are not only a source of (b)Grain(/b) but also (b)Straw(/b), which is a vital resource both as a building material and also as animal food.
	</string>
			
	<string name="help_defense_title">Defense</string>
	<string name="help_defense_description">
One of the keys to survival is to defend your settlement against hostile (b)animals(/b) and (b)raiders(/b).
During the (b)stone age(/b), the main threats are wild animals and sporadic bands of raiders. Make sure you have enough weapons and people to defend the settlement against them.
In the (b)metal age(/b) things will get more serious, and large bands of attackers will try to destroy your settlement. It is highly recommended that you build (b)fortifications(/b) and (b)defensive structures(/b).
At any time you can trigger an (b)alert(/b) in the defense panel, your people will then run back the settlement, get the best weapons available and man the towers.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_human_status_title">Human Status</string>
	<string name="help_human_status_description">
Humans have (b)health(/b), (b)nutrition(/b), (b)hydration(/b), (b)rest(/b), (b)temperature(/b), (b)stamina(/b) and (b)morale(/b) indicators that reflect their current status.
When an status indicator is low, a (b)warning sign(/b) will appear on top of that person, highlighting what's wrong with them.
Having sub-optimal status will make your people less effective, and eventually cause them to die. You need to monitor your people at all times and make sure their needs are fulfilled.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_health_title">Health</string>	
	<string name="help_health_description">
This is a measure of the physical health of a person. If it goes too low, the human will die.
(b)Health(/b) slowly recovers by itself in normal circumstances, unless the other status indicators are low or the human is affected by a (b)condition(/b).
    </string>	
	
	<string name="help_nutrition_title">Nutrition</string>	
	<string name="help_nutrition_description">
This is a measure of how well fed a person is. If it goes too low, (b)health(/b) will start to drop, and the human will eventually die.
(b)Nutrition(/b) can be recovered by eating food, which can be obtained from a variety of sources.
    </string>		
	
	<string name="help_hydration_title">Hydration</string>	
	<string name="help_hydration_description">
This is a measure of how thirsty a person is. If it goes too low, (b)health(/b) will start to drop, and the human will eventually die.
(b)Hydration(/b) can be recovered by drinking from a (b)river(/b), (b)lake(/b), (b)well(/b), or (b)stored water(/b).
    </string>	
	
	<string name="help_rest_title">Rest</string>	
	<string name="help_rest_description">
This is a measure how tired a person is. If it goes low, humans will be less effective at work.
(b)Rest(/b) can be recovered by sleeping in a (b)Tent(/b), (b)Hut(/b) or (b)Roundhouse(/b).
    </string>
	
	<string name="help_temperature_title">Temperature</string>	
	<string name="help_temperature_description">
This is a measure of the body temperature of a person. If it goes too low, (b)health(/b) will start to drop, and the human will eventually die.
To warm themselves up, humans can wear thicker clothing or shelter inside a (b)Tent(/b), (b)Hut(/b) or (b)Roundhouse(/b).
    </string>		
	
	<string name="help_stamina_title">Stamina</string>	
	<string name="help_stamina_description">
This is a measure of how out of breath a person is. if it goes too low, the human won't be able to run. It is an important factor in combat or when hunting.
(b)Stamina(/b) recovers automatically when idle.
    </string>		
	
	<string name="help_morale_title">Morale</string>	
	<string name="help_morale_description">
This is a measure of the psychological health of a person. If morale goes low, they will be (b)less effective at work(/b). Keeping morale high is therefore critical to the success of your settlement.
Morale can go down due to (b)hunger(/b), (b)deaths(/b), or performing (b)tedious tasks(/b), such as farming or carrying heavy loads.
Morale is increased by visiting one of the morale recovering structures like the (b)Skull Pole(/b), (b)Totem(/b), (b)Menhir(/b), (b)Dolmen(/b) or (b)Stone Circle(/b). More advanced morale structures recover more morale. 
A person has to wait a period of time before recovering again from the same type of structure, so it is important to build a variety of these.
Later in the game you can also produce (b)Beer(/b), which recovers a lot of morale, but needs to be made from Grain. 
	</string>			
	
  <string name="help_knowledge_title">Knowledge</string>
  <string name="help_knowledge_description">
You can earn (b)knowledge points(/b) in the game by achieving various goals:
• Reaching larger populations
• Building different types of structures
• Hunting different types of animals
• Acquiring the various resources
• Killing raiders
• Unlocking milestones
• Surviving more years
You can then use these points to unlock new (b)techs(/b), which allow you to advance your settlement and be able to sustain larger populations.
  </string>
	
	<string name="help_crafting_title">Crafting</string>
  <string name="help_crafting_description">
Your people can craft a variety of resources in the settlement's structures.
To craft a resource, select a (b)crafting structure(/b) and click on a recipe. If the resources are available, one of your people will craft it.
You can also right click on a recipe to toggle (b)continuous production(/b). When enabled your people will automatically produce the resource until the (b)resource limit(/b) is reached.
  </string>
	
	<string name="help_expanding_title">Expanding</string>
  <string name="help_expanding_description">
If your (b)welfare(/b) is high enough and you have enough capacity in your settlement, new people will come and join it, and your women will give (b)birth(/b) to new children.
You can increase your housing capacity by building (b)Tents(/b), (b)Huts(/b) or (b)Roundhouses(/b).
The frequency of migrant arrivals depends on your (b)welfare(/b) and (b)prestige(/b).
The fertility of your people also depends on your (b)welfare(/b) level.
  </string>	
  
  <string name="help_resource_limits_title">Resource Limits</string>
	<string name="help_resource_limits_description">
Resource Limits are a powerful way to automate work in your settlement.
You can set a (b)resource limit(/b), then mark a recipe for continuous production or place a work area: your people will keep on collecting or producing that resource until the limit is reached. 
When resources are consumed and the amounts fall below the limit again, your people will go back to work.
You can set any limit to 3 types of values:
(b)Infinity(/b). There's no limit to production, it will continue as long as there are materials available.
(b)Fixed amount(/b). Sets a limit defined by a specific number of units. Production stops once the number of units of that particular resource reaches the value.
(b)Population percentage(/b). Sets a limit defined by a percentage of the current population. Setting a percentage limit is useful to avoid having to constantly adjust the limits as the population changes.
Note that limits only affect work areas and automatic crafting, if you explicitly give an order, the limit is ignored.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_animal_limits_title">Animal Limits</string>
	<string name="help_animal_limits_description">
Animal Limits are an efficient way of controlling your domestic (b)animal population(/b), to ensure that they don't consume too much space or resources.
By (b)default(/b) only (b)very old animals(/b) will get slaughtered, as they would die of natural causes anyway.
However you can specify a (b)limit(/b) for each type of animal, and your people will (b)slaughter them automatically(/b) to keep the population under that amount.
Your people will slaughter the right animals to keep a good male/female ratio.
	</string>	
	
  <string name="help_resource_decay_title">Resource Decay</string>
  <string name="help_resource_decay_description">
Most resources and tools (b)decay(/b) over time, decay is also accelerated when tools are used.
Resources stored inside a structure, decay slowly. This is especially important for food, as it can mean the difference between having a good winter or massive starvation.
Some foods (b)decay very quickly(/b) like: Fruit, Berries or Raw Meat and Raw Fish.
Some foods (b)last a lot longer(/b) like: Grain, Cured Meat and Dry Fish.
Your people will try to eat the food that is going to decay sooner in order to preserve more durable food for later.
	</string>	
	
  <string name="help_workload_title">Workload</string>
  <string name="help_workload_description">
The (b)workload(/b) of your settlement is the ratio between the amount of tasks your people are trying to do, and the total amount of people.
If you ask your people to do too many things at once, they will be overworked, and will have trouble prioritizing the right tasks.
It is your job do make sure the amount of work to do is reasonable and proportional to the manpower available.
You can use the (b)tasks(/b) and (b)activity panels(/b) to see what your people are up to and how many of them are available to work.
	</string>
	
  <string name="help_human_roles_title">Human Roles</string>
  <string name="help_human_roles_description">
Depending on the age of your population they are able to perform different tasks:
(b)Children(/b). They can carry light resources around, one at a time, and do basic tasks that don't involve the usage of tools.
(b)Adults(/b). They are the most efficient of your people, they can carry a larger number of resources and perform any task.
(b)Elderly(/b). They can perform the same tasks as adults, but have less health and can carry less resources.
	</string>
  
  <string name="help_work_area_title">Work Areas</string>
  <string name="help_work_area_description">
Setting (b)work areas(/b) allows you to automate many of the (b)collection(/b) and (b)mining(/b) tasks in your settlement.
After you place an area for a given resource, people will keep collecting the resource within that area until the (b)resource limit(/b) is reached.
By default only one person at a time will work in a particular area, but you can increase their number in the selection panel.
Note that (b)hunting(/b) work areas will only generate tasks for animals of (b)low danger level(/b), dangerous animals have to be hunted manually.
  </string>
	
  <string name="help_foods_title">Foods</string>
  <string name="help_foods_description">
There are are different (b)types of food(/b) that your people can consume, it is important to understand the differences between them.
(b)Raw Fish(/b). Available all year long, every river or lake bank contains a certain amount of fish, once you exhaust it you need to wait for it to replenish. You can use the (b)Food Dryer(/b) to convert (b)Raw Fish(/b) to (b)Dry Fish(/b), which lasts a lot longer.
(b)Raw Meat(/b). You can hunt animals for their meat all year long, but in winter there will be a lot less of them around. You can use the (b)Food Dryer(/b) to convert (b)Raw Meat(/b) to (b)Cured Meat(/b), which lasts a lot longer.
(b)Berries(/b), (b)Fruit(/b) and (b)Nuts(/b). Available mostly in summer only, but some also in autumn. They don't last for long, but they are a good food to eat seasonally, so you can save non perishable foods for the winter.
(b)Pulses(/b). Available in summer, they require the right harvesting tools and technology to be processed. They last for a reasonable amount of time.
(b)Grain(/b). It lasts for an extremely long time, but requires processing to be eaten: First needs to be converted into (b)Flour(/b), then into (b)Bread(/b). This makes it quite labor intensive.
People will try to eat the foods that are about to perish first.
	</string>
	
  <string name="help_welfare_title">Welfare</string>
  <string name="help_welfare_description">
A measure of how well your settlement is doing.
Depends on your people's (b)stats(/b), (b)clothing(/b) and also on the (b)food surplus(/b).
If welfare is high (b)migrants(/b) will come to your settlement, the higher it is the more frequently they will arrive.
Welfare also affects the (b)birth rate(/b) in your settlement.
	</string>	
	
  <string name="help_prestige_title">Prestige</string>
  <string name="help_prestige_description">
A measure of how well known your settlement is.
Depends on your (b)population(/b), (b)buildings(/b) and (b)technology(/b).
If prestige is high (b)migrants(/b) and (b)traders(/b) will come more frequently to your settlement.
A good way to increase your settlement's (b)prestige(/b) is by constructing (b)megalithic(/b) structures.
	</string>		

	<!-- Conditions here refers to diseases or infections-->
  <string name="help_conditions_title">Conditions</string>
  <string name="help_conditions_description">
Humans can be affected by conditions such as (b)diseases(/b) or (b)infections(/b).
These are triggered from (b)going hungry(/b) repeatedly, or (b)sustaining injuries(/b).
When a person has a condition it's health will decrease for a given amount of time, if it reaches zero the person will die.
Survival chances are partly random and party based on how healthy the individual is.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_burials_title">Burials</string>
  <string name="help_burials_description">
When someone (b)dies(/b) the (b)morale(/b) of the people in your settlement (b)goes down(/b).
If there are any (b)burial structures(/b) available, your dead will be taken there. This will give your people a chance to (b)mourn(/b) them and (b)recover(/b) some of the lost (b)morale(/b).
Funerary structures have a (b)limited capacity(/b), when the structure is full no more people can be buried in it. Over time bodies decompose and the burial capacity of the structure is slowly restored.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_controls_title">Controls</string>	
	<string name="help_controls_description">
(b)CAMERA(/b)

Move: (camera_move_keys)
Rotate: (camera_rotate_keys)
Zoom: (b)Mouse Wheel(/b)


(b)SELECTION(/b)

Select entity: (b)Left mouse click(/b)
Select nearby similar entities: (b)Left mouse double click(/b)
Add/remove to/from selection:(b) Shift + Left mouse click(/b)

Select multiple entities: (b)Drag left mouse(/b)
Select hunters only: (b)Drag left mouse(/b) while holding the (hunter_selection_key) key
Select fighters only: (b)Drag left mouse(/b) while holding the (fighter_selection_key) key

Give command: (b)Right mouse click(/b)
Give command to sprint: (b)Right double click(/b)


(b)MANAGEMENT(/b)

Quick Save: (b)F9(/b)
Main Menu: (b)F10(/b)


(b)KEY BINDINGS(/b)

	</string>
	
	<string name="help_customizable_panels_title">Customizable Panels</string>	
	<string name="help_customizable_panels_description">
By pressing the (b)+(/b) buttons on the top part of the screen, you can (b)customize the info panels(/b).
You can get the UI to display the most (b)relevant information(/b) depending on your current situation.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_transport_title">Transportation</string>	
	<string name="help_transport_description">
(b)Transports(/b) will greatly increase the efficiency of your settlement.
Some resources, like (b)Logs(/b), (b)Stone(/b), (b)Copper Ore(/b), (b)Tin Ore(/b) or (b)Iron Ore(/b) are heavy and difficult to carry around.
Only adults can transport these, at a very slow speed, one at a time, and with a penalty to morale.
(b)Sledges(/b) and (b)Carts(/b) solve this problem, they allow you to transport several (b)heavy resources(/b) at a time a lot more efficiently.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_fuel_title">Fuel</string>	
	<string name="help_fuel_description">
In order to (b)cook food(/b) and stay warm you need to fuel your (b)Hearths(/b), (b)Huts(/b), (b)Roundhouses(/b) and (b)Ovens(/b).
You can use (b)Sticks(/b) or (b)Logs(/b) for this purpose. Your people will automatically refuel all structures unless you disable it in each structure.
	</string>
	
  <!-- === Main categories === -->
  
	<string name="help_structures_title">Structures</string>
	<string name="help_structures_description">
You can build many different structures in your settlement. Initially only a few are available, but you will unlock many more as the game progresses.</string>
	
	<string name="help_resources_title">Resources</string>
	<string name="help_resources_description">
You will need to manage a variety of Resources to keep your settlement running.
Most resources will decay and eventually become unusable, so you will need to continuously produce them.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_techs_title">Techs</string>
	<string name="help_techs_description">
Techs allow you to produce (b)more resources(/b), build (b)new structures(/b), and (b)move forward(/b) through the ages.
To research and unlock new techs, you need to spend knowledge points in the tech panel.
You earn (b)knowledge points(/b) when doing actions such as hunting animals, gathering resources, or achieving higher populations.
You can only unlock a Tech if you've previously unlocked it's (b)prerequisite techs(/b) and the (b)era(/b) it belongs to.
To unlock a new Era you need to unlock it's Era Tech, which requires twice as many Knowledge points to unlock.
    </string>
	
	<string name="help_animals_title">Animals</string>
	<string name="help_animals_description">	
Animals are the source of many key goods, such as (b)Raw Meat(/b), (b)Bones(/b), or (b)Raw Skins(/b). 
In (b)winter(/b) most animals will hibernate or migrate to warmer climates, so there will be less of them around.
Once you research the right domestication techs, you can capture young animals in order to breed them yourself.
	</string>

	<string name="help_transports_title">Attachments</string>
	<string name="help_transports_description">
(b)Attachments(/b) are used by your people to accomplish a variety of tasks.
Transports, like (b)Carts(/b) and (b)Sledges(/b) allow people to (b)carry resources(/b) much faster than they would otherwise do.
(b)Megaliths(/b) can only be moved using specialized transports.
(b)Plows(/b) allow you to plant crops much faster than doing it by hand.
	</string>
	
	
  <!-- === STRUCTURES: categories === -->
  
	<string name="help_buildable_category_residence_description">Structures that provide shelter for people or animals.</string>
	<string name="help_buildable_category_storage_description">Structures to store resources.</string>
	<string name="help_buildable_category_production_description">Structures to process resources.</string>
	<string name="help_buildable_category_defensive_description">Structures to help protect your settlement against (b)raiders(/b) or dangerous (b)predators(/b).</string>
	<string name="help_buildable_category_metallurgy_description">Structures for mining and processing metals.</string>
	<string name="help_buildable_category_spiritual_description">
Structures that improve your people's (b)Morale(/b).
When low on (b)Morale(/b), your people will visit a spiritual structure in order to recover it. Note that a person can not use the same type of structure too often, so it is important to build variety of these.
	</string>
	<string name="help_buildable_category_funerary_description">
Structures where you can (b)bury your dead(/b).
When someone dies, they will get taken to the nearest burial structure, where they can be mourned. This will allow your people to (b)recover morale(/b).
Each funerary structure has (b)limited capacity(/b), once it's full it can't be used anymore, but as bodies slowly decompose, the structure capacity (b)replenishes(/b) and you can bury people in it again. 
	</string>	
	<string name="help_buildable_category_transport_description">Structures that improve transport efficiency.</string>
	
  <!-- === Structures === -->

	<!-- === Residence === -->
	
	<string name="tent_short_description">A basic shelter</string>
	<string name="tent_help_description">
The earliest and most basic accommodation available, people can (b)rest(/b) and (b)shelter(/b) from the cold in it.
It deteriorates quickly and needs periodic maintenance.
It can be built from the (b)Paleolithic(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="hut_short_description">A hut with a thatched roof</string>
	<string name="hut_help_description">
A construction made out of (b)Mud(/b) with a thatched (b)Straw(/b) roof, people can (b)rest(/b), (b)shelter(/b) and (b)cook(/b) in it.
It is more durable than a (b)Tent(/b) and can house more people.
It require the (b)Thatching(/b) tech in order to be built.
	</string> 

	<string name="roundhouse_short_description">A circular stone house</string>
	<string name="roundhouse_help_description">
A construction made of (b)Stone(/b) with a thatched (b)Straw(/b) roof, people can (b)rest(/b), (b)shelter(/b) and (b)cook(/b) in it.
It is more durable than a (b)Hut(/b) and can house more people.
It requires the (b)Masonry(/b) tech in order to be built.
	</string>
	
	<string name="stables_short_description">A place to keep domestic animals</string>
	<string name="stables_help_description">
A place for (b)domestic animals(/b) to (b)shelter(/b) in winter and be fed and watered.
It needs periodic maintenance.
	</string>
	
	<string name="stone_stables_short_description">A larger and more durable place to keep domestic animals</string>
	<string name="stone_stables_help_description">
A place for (b)domestic animals(/b) to (b)shelter(/b) in winter and be fed and watered.
It needs periodic maintenance.
	</string>	
	
	<!-- === Storage === -->
	
	<string name="storage_tent_short_description">A basic storage structure</string>
	<string name="storage_tent_help_description">
A large tent built for storing and (b)preserving resources(/b) for longer.
It deteriorates quickly and needs periodic maintenance.
It can be built from the (b)Paleolithic(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="wood_pile_short_description">A place to store Sticks and Logs</string>
	<string name="wood_pile_help_description">
A place to stack (b)Sticks(/b) or (b)Logs(/b), rather than using residence or other storage structures, which wastes valuable space.
	</string>
	
	<string name="haystack_short_description">A place to store Straw</string>
	<string name="haystack_help_description">
A place to store (b)Straw(/b), rather than using residence or other storage structures, which wastes valuable space.
	</string>
	
	<string name="storage_hut_short_description">A hut to store and preserve resources</string>
	<string name="storage_hut_help_description">
A large construction made out of (b)Mud(/b) with a thatched (b)Straw(/b) roof, where resources can be stored and preserved for longer.
It is more durable than a (b)Storage Tent(/b) and can store more resources for longer.
Requires the (b)Thatching(/b) tech in order to be built.
	</string>
	
	<string name="granary_short_description">A structure to preserve food</string>
	<string name="granary_help_description">
A raised hut, purpose built to keep food dry and preserved for (b)as long as possible(/b).  
Granaries are reasonably durable, but they need repairing from time to time.
Requires the (b)Thatching(/b) tech in order to be built.
	</string>
	
	<string name="staddle_granary_short_description">A larger and more durable structure to preserve food</string>
	<string name="staddle_granary_help_description">
A raised structure, built to keep food dry and preserved for (b)as long as possible(/b).  
It's more durable than a (b)Granary(/b) and can store more food.
Requires the (b)Staddle Stones(/b) tech in order to be built.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="rock_pile_short_description">A place to store Flint, Stone or Ores</string>
	<string name="rock_pile_help_description">
A place to store (b)Flint(/b), (b)Stone(/b) or (b)ores(/b), rather than using residence or other storage structures, which wastes valuable space.
	</string>

	<string name="warehouse_short_description">A stone house to store and preserve resources</string>
	<string name="warehouse_help_description">
A large construction made out of (b)Stone(/b) with a thatched (b)Straw(/b) roof, where resources can be stored and preserved for longer.
It is more durable than a (b)Storage Hut(/b) and can store more resources for longer.
Requires the (b)Masonry(/b) tech in order to be built.
	</string>	
	
	<!-- === Production === -->
	
	<string name="hearth_short_description">A place to cook, make bread and socialize</string>
	<string name="hearth_help_description">
A common place where to cook food and make bread.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="crafter_short_description">A place to create tools and clothing</string>
	<string name="crafter_help_description">
The Crafter is the main production structure in the (b)Stone Age(/b).
In it your people can create all the (b)tools(/b) and (b)clothing(/b) they will need in the early eras.
It is a good idea to use (b)automated production(/b) (by right clicking on an item) and (b)resource limits(/b) in order to avoid to have to manually craft tools every time you need them.
	</string>
	
	<string name="skins_dryer_short_description">A place to dry skins</string>
	<string name="skins_dryer_help_description">
A structure where your people will transform (b)Raw Skins(/b) into (b)Dry Skins(/b), that are more durable and usable.
	</string>
	
	<string name="food_dryer_short_description">A place to dry food</string>
	<string name="food_dryer_help_description">
A structure where (b)Raw Meat(/b) and (b)Fish(/b) can be processed into (b)Cured Meat(/b) and (b)Dry Fish(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="mortar_short_description">A rock to crush Grain into Flour</string>
	<string name="mortar_help_description">
A rock to crush (b)Grain(/b) into (b)Flour(/b). This is quite a labor intensive process. 
	</string>
	
	<string name="tanner_short_description">A place to make Leather from Raw Skins</string>
	<string name="tanner_help_description">
A place where (b)Raw Skins(/b) can be treated with (b)Tannin(/b) in order to make (b)Leather(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="well_short_description">A hole in the ground to extract water</string>
	<string name="well_help_description">
Wells provide settlements with a steady source of (b)Water(/b), they can be placed within the settlement's walls in order to avoid people having to go to the nearest river or lake.
	</string>
	
	<string name="flint_mine_short_description">An underground structure to increase Flint extraction</string>
	<string name="flint_mine_help_description">
(b)Increases(/b) the amount of (b)Flint(/b) that can be extracted from a deposit.
	</string>
	
	<string name="weaver_short_description">A place to make cloth</string>
	<string name="weaver_help_description">
A place where (b)Linen(/b) and (b)Wool(/b) are woven to create cloth, that can then be used to make outfits.
	</string>

	<string name="outfitter_short_description">A place to create clothing</string>
	<string name="outfitter_help_description">
A place where outfits are made from (b)Linen Cloth(/b) and (b)Wool Cloth(/b).
	</string>	

	<string name="brewery_short_description">A place to brew Beer</string>
	<string name="brewery_help_description">
A facility where your people can make (b)Beer(/b) from (b)Grain(/b) and (b)Water(/b).
(b)Beer(/b) increases morale in your settlement.
	</string>

	<string name="watermill_short_description">A place to crush grain using hydropower</string>
	<string name="watermill_help_description">
A place where to efficiently crush large quantities of (b)Grain(/b) into (b)Flour(/b) using hydropower.
	</string>

	<string name="oven_short_description">A communal oven to bake Bread in large quantities</string>
	<string name="oven_help_description">
A place where to efficiently bake large quantities of (b)Bread(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="workshop_short_description">A place to make miscellaneous tools</string>
	<string name="workshop_help_description">
A place to make tools from the (b)Copper Age(/b) onward.
This structure in combination with the (b)Metalsmith(/b) or (b)Blacksmith(/b) serves as replacement for the (b)Crafter(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<!-- === Metallurgy === -->
		
	<string name="copper_mine_short_description">An underground structure to increase Copper Ore extraction</string>
	<string name="copper_mine_help_description">
An underground excavation that (b)increases(/b) the amount of (b)Copper Ore(/b) that can be extracted from a deposit.
	</string>

	<string name="tin_mine_short_description">An underground structure to increase Tin Ore extraction</string>
	<string name="tin_mine_help_description">
An underground excavation that (b)increases(/b) the amount of (b)Tin Ore(/b) that can be extracted from a deposit.
	</string>
	
	<string name="iron_mine_short_description">An underground structure to increase Iron Ore extraction</string>
	<string name="iron_mine_help_description">
An underground excavation that (b)increases(/b) the amount of (b)Iron Ore(/b) that can be extracted from a deposit.
	</string>

	<string name="deep_iron_mine_short_description">A deep underground structure to further increase Iron Ore extraction</string>
	<string name="deep_iron_mine_help_description">
A deep underground excavation that (b)increases(/b) the amount of (b)Iron Ore(/b) that can be extracted from a deposit.
Once the original ore is exhausted and your people have to go deeper down, (b)mining speed(/b) is (b)reduced(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="charcoal_pit_short_description">A place to make Charcoal from wood</string>
	<string name="charcoal_pit_help_description">
A place to make (b)Charcoal(/b) from wood.
(b)Charcoal(/b) is then used in the furnaces to smelt ores into metals.
	</string>

	<string name="pit_furnace_short_description">A place to smelt Copper and Tin Ores into Copper and Bronze</string>
	<string name="pit_furnace_help_description">
A basic furnace where (b)Charcoal(/b) is used in order to attain the high temperatures required to smelt (b)Copper Ore(/b) and (b)Tin Ore(/b) into (b)Copper(/b) and (b)Bronze(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="metalsmith_short_description">A place to make Copper and Bronze tools</string>
	<string name="metalsmith_help_description">
A place to create (b)Copper(/b) and (b)Bronze(/b) tools and weapons.
Note that only one person can work in it at a time, so you will usually need a few of these.
	</string>

	<string name="bloomery_short_description">A place to smelt Iron Ore into Iron and Steel</string>
	<string name="bloomery_help_description">
An advanced furnace, where very high temperatures can be reached in order to smelt (b)Iron Ore(/b) into (b)Iron(/b) and (b)Steel(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="blacksmith_short_description">A place to make Iron and Steel tools</string>
	<string name="blacksmith_help_description">
A place to create (b)Iron(/b) and (b)Steel(/b) tools and weapons.
Note that only one person can work in it at a time, so you will usually need a few of these.
	</string>

	<!-- === Defensive === -->

	<string name="palisade_short_description">Simple wooden structure to protect the settlement</string>
	<string name="palisade_help_description">
Simple wooden structure to protect the settlement. It's made from (b)Logs(/b) and offers a reasonable level of protection.
	</string>

	<string name="gate_short_description">Simple wooden gate, to control access to your settlement</string>
	<string name="gate_help_description">
A simple wooden gate, that can resist attacks for a reasonable amount of time.
	</string>
	
	<string name="wooden_platform_short_description">A structure for your people to shoot at enemies from inside the settlement's walls</string>
	<string name="wooden_platform_help_description">
A structure for your people to shoot at enemies from (b)inside(/b) the settlement's walls.
Warriors on a platform have (b)extra protection(/b) from incoming projectiles.
Needs to be placed next to a (b)Palisade(/b) or (b)Wall(/b) on the inner side.
	</string>	

	<string name="watchtower_short_description">Basic tower, from which to shoot at enemies</string>
	<string name="watchtower_help_description">
The most basic defense tower. Up to 2 people can shelter in it and (b)shoot(/b) at incoming enemies.
They require periodic (b)repairs(/b) and maintenance.
	</string>

	<string name="wall_short_description">A sturdy Stone wall to protect the settlement</string>
	<string name="wall_help_description">
A durable (b)Stone(/b) wall, that offers the highest level of protection available against intruders.
	</string>

	<string name="reinforced_gate_short_description">A metal reinforced gate</string>
	<string name="reinforced_gate_help_description">
A gate (b)reinforced(/b) with (b)metal(/b) in order to increase its resistance against attacks.
	</string>
	
	<string name="reinforced_platform_short_description">A reinforced platform that can hold more people</string>
	<string name="reinforced_platform_help_description">
A structure for your people to shoot at enemies from (b)inside(/b) the settlement's walls.
Warriors on a platform have (b)extra protection(/b) from incoming projectiles.
Needs to be placed next to a (b)Palisade(/b) or (b)Wall(/b) on the inner side.
This structure can hold more people and is more resistant than the (b)Wooden Platform(/b).
	</string>		

	<string name="guard_tower_short_description">A reinforced defense tower</string>
	<string name="guard_tower_help_description">
A reinforced defense tower. Up to 3 people can shelter in it and shoot at incoming enemies. 
Guard Towers require periodic repairs and maintenance.
	</string>
	
	<!-- === Spiritual === -->

	<string name="burial_mound_short_description">A place to bury your dead</string>
	<string name="burial_mound_help_description">
A small tomb where to (b)bury your dead(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="skull_pole_short_description">A structure in memory of the fallen ancestors</string>
	<string name="skull_pole_help_description">
A structure in memory of the fallen ancestors, that your people can visit in order to recover (b)Morale(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="totem_short_description">A structure to honor nature</string>
	<string name="totem_help_description">
A tall, powerful symbol of both the tribe itself and its relation with nature. Your people can use it to recover (b)Morale(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="menhir_short_description">A standing Megalith</string>
	<string name="menhir_help_description">
A large standing (b)Megalith(/b). Your people can use it to recover (b)Morale(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="dolmen_short_description">A large funerary structure made of several stones supporting a bigger rock</string>
	<string name="dolmen_help_description">
A funerary chamber consisting of several supporting pillars, and one or more stones placed on top. It increases your settlement's (b)prestige(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="stone_circle_short_description">A structure made of several megaliths arranged in a circle</string>
	<string name="stone_circle_help_description">
A large structure composed by several (b)Megaliths(/b) arranged in a circle. It greatly increases your settlement's (b)prestige(/b) and provides a boost for your people's (b)Morale(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="statue_short_description">A carved Megalith</string>
	<string name="statue_help_description">
A carved standing (b)Megalith(/b). Your people can use it to recover (b)Morale(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="banner_short_description">A symbol of a settlement's power</string>
	<string name="banner_help_description">
A symbol of a settlement's power. Your people can use it to recover (b)Morale(/b).
	</string>		
	
	<string name="cairn_short_description">A megalithic funerary complex</string>
	<string name="cairn_help_description">
A megalithic funerary complex built with rocks of various sizes. It greatly increases your settlement's (b)prestige(/b).
	</string>	
	
	
	<!-- === Transport === -->
	<string name="bridge_short_description">A structure to allow easier crossing of rivers</string>
	<string name="bridge_help_description">
A structure in order to ease the (b)crossing of rivers(/b).
This is especially useful for (b)Sledges(/b) and (b)Carts(/b) as otherwise they have to cross via the nearest ford.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="transport_post_short_description">A place to leave transports</string>
	<string name="transport_post_help_description">
A place to leave (b)transports(/b) and (b)Plows(/b).
Your people will carry (b)Sledges(/b) here when they are not in use.
Any animals that are pulling (b)Carts(/b) or (b)Plows(/b) will automatically come here when idle.
	</string>		

  <!-- === RESOURCES: Categories === -->
  
	<string name="help_category_tool_description">
Tools are required to perform certain tasks such as hunting, butchering, mining, fishing, or harvesting. Your people will automatically fetch the right tool for the job before doing it.
Each tool has a series of attributes that indicate how suitable the tool is to perform certain tasks:
(b)Fighting.(/b) Hand to hand combat.
(b)Hunting.(/b) Killing animals or ranged combat.
(b)Butchering.(/b) Butchering dead animals and extracting their resources.
(b)Fishing.(/b) Extracting fish from rivers or lakes.
(b)Harvesting.(/b) Harvesting cereals or pulses.
(b)Mining.(/b) Extracting ores from deposits or mines.
(b)Woodcutting.(/b) Cut down trees.
Fighting and hunting attributes affect damage dealt in combat, other attributes affect the speed at which the task is done.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_category_clothing_description">
Clothing offers your people protection from cold, increases welfare and reduces damage sustained in combat.
(b)Skins(/b) and (b)Wool(/b) outfits protect people up to freezing temperatures. It is (b)critical(/b) that you have one of these per inhabitant.
When it is warm your people will prefer to wear (b)Leather(/b) or (b)Linen(/b) outfits, these increase (b)welfare(/b) levels and offer slight protection in combat.
A typical way to ensure you have enough clothing is to set outfits to continuous production in the (b)Crafter(/b) or (b)Outfitter(/b) structures and having a resource limit set of 100%.
When the temperature drops below the level of protection clothing offers, the temperature of the person will start to drop, at this point they will have to seek (b)shelter(/b) or they will die of (b)hypothermia(/b).	
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_category_food_and_drink_description">
Resources that can be consumed to recover (b)Nutrition(/b) and (b)Hydration(/b) levels.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_category_material_description">
Resources used to (b)craft(/b) or (b)build(/b) other resources or structures.
	</string>
	
  <!-- === Tools === -->

	<string name="biface_short_description">General purpose cutting tool</string>
	<string name="biface_help_description">
Basic cutting tool, used to (b)butcher(/b) animals, (b)harvest(/b) plants or as a simple hand to hand combat (b)weapon(/b).
Bifaces are classified as a knives rather than axes, based on the functions they perform.
	</string>
	
	<string name="wooden_spear_short_description">Basic hunting tool</string>
	<string name="wooden_spear_help_description">
The most basic (b)hunting(/b) and (b)ranged combat(/b) tool. A simple wooden spear with a fire hardened tip.
	</string>	

	<string name="spear_short_description">Hunting tool</string>
	<string name="spear_help_description">
Spears can be used to (b)hunt(/b) animals or (b)fight(/b) enemies. They are made out of a wooden shaft, and a head made out of a different material, like (b)Bone(/b), (b)Flint(/b) or (b)Metal(/b).
They are better used in ranged combat, but if required can also be employed at melee range, with reduced effectiveness.
	</string>

	<string name="harpoon_short_description">Fishing tool</string>
	<string name="harpoon_help_description">
Harpoons are purpose built tools for (b)fishing(/b). They are made out of a wooden shaft and a head designed to catch fish.
	</string>  

	<string name="fishing_rod_short_description">Specialized fishing tool</string>
	<string name="fishing_rod_help_description">
Very (b)effective fishing(/b) tool used to catch almost any kind of fish.
	</string>  	
	
	<string name="fish_trap_short_description">Advanced fishing tool</string>
	<string name="fish_trap_help_description">
Extremely (b)effective fishing(/b) tool used to catch almost any kind of fish.
	</string>  		
	
	<string name="axe_short_description">Woodcutting and fighting tool</string>
	<string name="axe_help_description">
Axes are useful to (b)cut down(/b) trees or as hand to hand combat (b)weapons(/b). They have different resistances and strengths depending of whether they are made of (b)Flint(/b) or (b)metal(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="pick_short_description">Tool to mine ores or rocks.</string>
	<string name="pick_help_description">
Picks are used primarily for (b)breaking rocks(/b) and (b)mining(/b) various ores. They are composed of a wooden handle and a sharp, hard point made of (b)Flint(/b) or (b)metal(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="knife_short_description">Tool used primarily to butcher animals</string>
	<string name="knife_help_description">
Knives are used mainly for (b)butchering(/b) dead animals and (b)slaughtering(/b) domestic animals.
They can also be used in melee (b)combat(/b) if required. 
They are made out of a wooden handle, and a blade of (b)Flint(/b) or (b)metal(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="sickle_short_description">Harvesting tool</string>
	<string name="sickle_help_description">
Sickles are specialized tools designed to (b)harvest(/b) crops. The better the material of the blade, the more effective the tool.
	</string>  

	<string name="bow_short_description">Hunting and ranged combat weapon</string>  
	<string name="bow_help_description">
Excellent (b)ranged(/b) attack (b)weapon(/b), used to (b)hunt(/b) or (b)fight(/b) enemies at a distance.
Bows have a longer range than spears, but are ineffective at close quarters.
	</string>    

	<string name="sling_short_description">Basic hunting tool</string>
	<string name="sling_help_description">
The sling is a basic, easy to make (b)ranged(/b) weapon, used mostly for (b)hunting(/b).
Slings have a longer range than spears, but are ineffective at close quarters.
	</string>  
	
	<string name="sword_short_description">Hand to hand combat weapon</string>
	<string name="sword_help_description">
Swords are the most effective (b)melee combat(/b) weapon of the ancient times. They consist of a wooden handle and a sharp blade made of metal.
	</string>
	
	<string name="round_shield_short_description">Small Shield that provides basic protection</string>
	<string name="round_shield_help_description">
A small round shield made of wood with a Leather cover. Offers basic protection in combat. 
Can be used with one handed weapons like (b)Swords(/b) or (b)Axes(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="oval_shield_short_description">Large Shield that provides good protection</string>
	<string name="oval_shield_help_description">
A large oval shield made of wood with an Iron core. Offers good protection in combat. 
Can be used with one handed weapons like (b)Swords(/b) or (b)Axes(/b).
	</string>		

  <!-- === Materials === -->
  
	<string name="sticks_help_description">
Used as crafting or construction materials or as fuel in (b)Hearths(/b), (b)Huts(/b), (b)Ovens(/b) or (b)Roundhouses(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="log_help_description">
Logs can be used in construction or as fuel in (b)Hearths(/b), (b)Huts(/b), (b)Ovens(/b) or (b)Roundhouses(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="flint_help_description">
A valuable crafting material, used to make all sorts of (b)tools(/b) in the (b)Stone Age(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="stone_help_description">
A large rock used to construct sturdy structures.
	</string>

	<string name="megalith_help_description">
A giant rock that can be used to build (b)megalithic structures(/b).
Megaliths need to be mined first, then get ready for transport and finally pulled by humans to the construction site.
You can use (b)primal vision(/b) in order to find and track megaliths.
	</string>
	
	<string name="bone_help_description">
Used as a crafting or construction material.
	</string>

	<string name="raw_skin_help_description">
Raw skin from an animal, it needs to be (b)dried(/b) or (b)treated(/b) before it can be used.
	</string>
	
	<string name="dry_skin_short_description">A dry skin</string>	
	<string name="dry_skin_help_description">
A dry skin, used for (b)crafting(/b) tools or (b)building(/b) structures.
	</string>
	
	<string name="leather_short_description">A skin which has been tanned to make it more durable</string>	
	<string name="leather_help_description">
A (b)skin(/b) which has been (b)tanned(/b) to make it more (b)durable(/b). Leather can be used to craft clothing and tools or construct structures.
	</string>
	
	<string name="tannin_help_description">
A substance used to treat (b)Raw Skins(/b) in order to make (b)Leather(/b). It is obtained from the bark of some trees, such as (b)Oaks(/b) and (b)Firs(/b). 
	</string>
	
	<string name="straw_help_description">
(b)Straw(/b) is obtained when harvesting cereals. It is a very important resource from the Neolithic onward, both as a (b)construction(/b) material and as (b)animal fodder(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="mud_help_description">
Used as (b)construction material(/b), mud can be (b)extracted(/b) from (b)rivers(/b) and (b)lakes(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="wool_help_description">
A textile fiber obtained from the hair of sheep, used to make (b)warm clothing(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="linen_help_description">
A textile fiber obtained from flax plants, used to make clothing and other resources.
	</string>

	<string name="wool_cloth_short_description">Cloth used to make warm outfits</string>	
	<string name="wool_cloth_help_description">
Cloth with excellent insulating properties used to create (b)warm clothing(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="linen_cloth_short_description">Cloth used in light outfits</string>
	<string name="linen_cloth_help_description">
Cloth used to make light outfits.
	</string>

	<string name="charcoal_short_description">Used in furnaces in order to smelt ores</string>
	<string name="charcoal_help_description">
A byproduct of (b)wood(/b) heated in the absence of oxygen, it is required for the furnaces to reach the high temperatures required for the (b)smelting(/b) of (b)ores(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="copper_ore_help_description">
An ore containing copper. Can be smelted into (b)Copper(/b), or mixed with (b)Tin Ore(/b) to make (b)Bronze(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="tin_ore_help_description">
An ore containing tin. Can be mixed with (b)Copper Ore(/b) to produce (b)Bronze(/b).
	</string>		
	
	<string name="iron_ore_help_description">
An ore containing iron. Can be smelted to produce (b)Iron(/b) or (b)Steel(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="copper_short_description">A soft metal</string>
	<string name="copper_help_description">
A (b)soft metal(/b), easy to obtain and work into basic tools.
	</string>	

	<string name="bronze_short_description">A hard and durable metal</string>
	<string name="bronze_help_description">
An alloy of (b)Copper Ore(/b) and (b)Tin Ore(/b), much harder than (b)Copper(/b).
(b)Bronze(/b) is as hard as (b)Iron(/b) but it requires tin to be created, which is not a widely available as (b)Iron Ore(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="iron_short_description">A hard and durable metal</string>		
	<string name="iron_help_description">
Iron is a (b)hard and durable(/b) metal, used to craft many tools, weapons and also used in construction.
It requires higher temperatures to be smelted when compared to (b)Bronze(/b), so it has to be produced in special furnaces.
Its main advantage over (b)Bronze(/b) is that (b)Iron Ore(/b) is a lot more abundant than (b)Tin Ore(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="steel_short_description">A very hard and durable metal</string>			
	<string name="steel_help_description">
(b)Steel(/b) is obtained by carefully controlling the amount of carbon mixed with the iron in the smelting process. It is the (b)hardest and most durable(/b) metal available.
	</string>
	
  <!-- === Food and drink === -->
  
	<string name="raw_meat_help_description">
Meat that hasn't been processed in any way, will (b)decay quickly(/b) if left as is.
It can be (b)cooked(/b) in order to be eaten. In extreme cases it could be eaten as is, but this will cause morale to decay.
	</string>

	<string name="cured_meat_short_description">Meat that has been cured. Lasts for a long time</string>
	<string name="cured_meat_help_description">
Meat that has been processed in the (b)Food Dryer(/b). It lasts a (b)lot longer(/b) than (b)Raw Meat(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="raw_fish_help_description">
Fish hasn't been processed in any way since capture. (b)Decays very quickly(/b).
It can be (b)cooked(/b) in order to be eaten. In extreme cases it could be eaten as is, but this will cause morale to decay.
	</string>

	<string name="dry_fish_short_description">Fish that has been dried. Lasts for a long time</string>		
	<string name="dry_fish_help_description">
Fish that has been processed in the (b)Food Dryer(/b). It lasts a (b)lot longer(/b) than (b)Raw Fish(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="berries_help_description">
Seasonal fruits produced by some wild plants. 
They don't last for long, but are good to (b)eat(/b) when in (b)season(/b) in order to keep more durable food for the winter.
	</string>
	
	<string name="fruit_help_description">
Seasonal fruit produced by some wild trees. 
It doesn't last for long, but is good to (b)eat(/b) when in (b)season(/b) in order to keep more durable food for the winter.
	</string>
	
	<string name="nuts_help_description">
Seasonal nuts produced by some wild trees. 
They don't last for long, but are good to (b)eat(/b) when in (b)season(/b) in order to keep more durable food for the winter.
	</string>
	
	<string name="grain_help_description">
Used to make (b)Flour(/b), which in turn can be transformed into (b)Bread(/b). It is also a key ingredient in (b)Beer(/b), which boosts morale.
It is the (b)most durable(/b) type of food available, and the best resource to feed (b)large amounts of people(/b), even if processing it is quite labor intensive.
It can also serve as animal fodder if required, but it is better to use (b)Straw(/b) instead.
	</string>
	
	<string name="flour_short_description">The main ingredient of Bread</string>	
	<string name="flour_help_description">
A powder obtained from crushing (b)Grain(/b) either in a (b)Mortar(/b) or a (b)Watermill(/b). 
It is the main ingredient of (b)Bread(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="bread_short_description">Simple flour bread</string>		
	<string name="bread_help_description">
A food obtained by baking (b)Flour(/b) and water in a (b)Hearth(/b) or (b)Oven(/b).
It doesn't last for long so it's better to store (b)Grain(/b) and only produce (b)Bread(/b) right before it is consumed.
	</string>
	
	<string name="pulses_help_description">
The seeds of many types of legume fruits. They need to be (b)cooked(/b) before they can be eaten.
	</string>
	
	<string name="milk_help_description">
A nutritious drink obtained from domestic (b)Goats(/b) or (b)Cattle(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="water_help_description">
Having dedicated water collectors that carry water from rivers, lakes, or wells is more (b)efficient(/b) that having everyone go to the water source every time.
Stabled (b)animals(/b) need to be brought (b)Water(/b) in (b)winter(/b), or they will die of thirst.
	</string>
	
	<string name="beer_short_description">Recovers morale and hydration</string>		
	<string name="beer_help_description">
A mild alcoholic drink obtained by brewing (b)Grain(/b) with (b)Water(/b). It boosts the (b)Morale(/b) of your people.
	</string>
	
	
  <!-- === Clothing === -->

	<string name="skins_outfit_short_description">Warm outfit made of animal hide</string>
	<string name="skins_outfit_help_description">
An outfit made from animal (b)skins(/b), which offers excellent (b)protection(/b) against the (b)cold(/b) in winter.
It also increases (b)welfare(/b), and offers slight protection in combat.
	</string>

	<string name="leather_outfit_short_description">Light outfit made of leather</string>
	<string name="leather_outfit_help_description">
Clothing made from (b)Leather(/b), to be worn during warm seasons.
It also increases (b)welfare(/b), and offers slight protection in combat.
	</string>
	
	<string name="wool_outfit_short_description">Warm and stylish outfit</string>
	<string name="wool_outfit_help_description">
A warm outfit to (b)protect(/b) from the (b)cold(/b) in low temperatures.
It also increases (b)welfare(/b), and offers slight protection in combat.
(b)Wool Outfits(/b) are more (b)durable(/b) than (b)Skins Outfits(/b), and provide more (b)welfare(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="linen_outfit_short_description">Light and stylish outfit</string>
	<string name="linen_outfit_help_description">
A light outfit to wear in warm temperatures.
It also increases (b)welfare(/b), and offers slight protection in combat.
(b)Linen Outfits(/b) are more (b)durable(/b) than (b)Leather Outfits(/b), and provide more (b)welfare(/b).
	</string>	
	
  <!-- === TECHS: categories === -->
	
	<string name="help_era_paleolithic_description">
A period where humans lived mostly in (b)hunter-gatherer(/b) bands that used tools made of (b)stone(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_era_mesolithic_description">
A period where humans started to make (b)pottery(/b) and more sophisticated (b)stone tools(/b).    
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_era_neolithic_description">
A period where humans started to (b)domesticate plants(/b) and (b)animals(/b) and made rapid technological advances.  
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_era_copper_age_description">
A period where humans discovered how to (b)smelt copper(/b) in order to create the first metal tools.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_era_bronze_age_description">
A period where humans discovered how to mix tin and copper and lead to the widespread use of (b)Bronze(/b) tools and objects.
	</string>

	<string name="help_era_iron_age_description">
A period characterized by the widespread use of (b)Iron(/b) tools and objects. 
	</string>

	<!-- === Generic === -->
	
	<string name="domestication_tech_help_description">
Domestication techs allow you to (b)tame wild animals(/b).
Once the tech is researched you will be able to (b)capture wild animals(/b) or (b)purchase(/b)  them from traders.
To capture a wild animal you need to select a young animal of the right type and then click on the capture button.
Make sure to have enough capacity in your (b)Stables(/b), otherwise the animals will die in winter.
	</string>
	
	<!-- === Paleolithic === -->

	<string name="bone_tools_help_description">
Unlocks the creation of (b)tools(/b) made using animal (b)bones(/b), which are effective for certain tasks.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="composite_tools_help_description">
Unlocks the creation of tools composed of (b)several parts(/b). Composite tools are very useful for (b)hunting(/b) larger animals or (b)cutting down(/b) trees.
	</string> 	
	
	<string name="slingmaking_help_description">
Allows you to make (b)Slings(/b), which are basic hunting tools.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="food_drying_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of the (b)Food Dryer(/b), where you can produce (b)Cured Meat(/b) and (b)Dry Fish(/b), which are the only long lasting foods available in the (b)Paleolithic(/b).
	</string> 
	
	<string name="dog_domestication_help_description">
Unlocks the domestication of (b)Dogs(/b). Dogs will slowly come to the settlement and will help you protect it.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="dog_training_help_description">
Unlocks the ability for (b)Dogs(/b) to help humans in hunting tasks.
	</string> 	
	
	<string name="tanning_help_description">
Unlocks the (b)Tanner(/b), where you can produce (b)Leather(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="spirituality_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of the (b)Totem(/b) structure, which helps with keeping morale high in the settlement.
	</string> 	
	
	<string name="funerary_rituals_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of the (b)Burial Mound(/b) structure, where you can bury your dead.
	</string> 		
 
 <!-- === Mesolithic === -->
 
	<string name="stone_polishing_help_description">
Unlocks (b)polished(/b) stone tools in the (b)Crafter(/b).
	</string> 
	
	<string name="bone_polishing_help_description">
Unlocks (b)polished(/b) bone tools in the (b)Crafter(/b).
	</string> 	
	
	<string name="pottery_help_description">
Unlocks the (b)Mesolithic(/b) era, and also the ability to (b)transport(/b) and (b)store Water(/b). 
This is a lot more efficient than having people going to the water source every time.
	</string> 

	<string name="archery_help_description">
Unlocks the creation of (b)Bows(/b), which are the best hunting tool available in the (b)Stone Age(/b).
	</string> 

	<string name="grain_processing_help_description">
Allows you to harvest (b)wild cereals(/b), crush them into (b)Flour(/b) and make (b)Bread(/b).
	</string> 

	<string name="pulse_processing_help_description">
Allows you to harvest (b)wild pulses(/b) and cook them.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="sledgemaking_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Sledges(/b), which are a critical transport in the early eras.
	</string> 
	
 <!-- === Neolithic === -->
 
	<string name="underground_mining_help_description">
Allows you to build mines on top of deposits. Mines dramatically (b)increase(/b) the amount of (b)resources(/b) you can extract from a (b)deposit(/b).
	</string> 
	
	<string name="deep_mining_help_description">
Allows you to build deep mines, which (b)further increase(/b) the amount of (b)resources(/b) that can be extracted from a (b)deposit(/b).
	</string> 	
	
	<string name="thatching_help_description">
Unlocks (b)thatched structures(/b), which are in general more durable and advanced than skins structures.
	</string> 

	<string name="well_digging_help_description">
Allows you to make (b)Wells(/b), that are more efficient than having to go collect water from the nearest river or lake.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="fortifications_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of basic (b)defensive structures(/b) that can be used to protect your settlement against (b)raiders(/b) and (b)predators(/b) in order to minimize the loss of life.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="reinforced_fortifications_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Reinforced Gates(/b) and (b)Guard Towers(/b).
These are more durable than their wooden counterparts, and in the case of the (b)Guard Tower(/b) can hold more people.
	</string> 	
	
	<string name="cereal_domestication_help_description">
It allows you to (b)plant(/b) and (b)harvest cereals(/b), unlocking the (b)Neolithic(/b) era.
It dramatically (b)increases(/b) the amount of (b)people(/b) you can reliably (b)feed(/b) every year.
This is one of the most important techs in the history of mankind.
	</string> 
	
	<string name="pulse_domestication_help_description">
Allows you to (b)plant(/b) and (b)harvest pulses(/b). 
Pulses are usually harvested in summer, so they are a good complement to cereals which are harvested in the fall.
	</string>
	
	<string name="flax_domestication_help_description">
Allows you to plant (b)Flax(/b), which is used to produce (b)Linen Cloth(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="weaving_help_description">
Allows you to make cloth and outfits made of (b)Linen(/b) and (b)Wool(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="netting_help_description">
Allows you to make (b)Fishing Nets(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="stilting_help_description">
Allows you to build (b)Bridges(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="megalithism_help_description">
Allows you to build (b)megalithic structures(/b) that increase the settlement's (b)prestige(/b) and help improve (b)morale(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="stone_carving_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Statues(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="complex_megalithism_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of complex (b)megalithic structures(/b) that increase the settlement's (b)prestige(/b) and help improve (b)morale(/b).
	</string>
	
 <!-- === Copper Age === -->
 
	<string name="copper_smelting_help_description">
Unlocks the production of (b)Copper(/b) in (b)Pit Furnaces(/b), the (b)Metalsmith(/b) structure and the creation of (b)Copper(/b) tools and weapons.
Unlocks the (b)Copper Age(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="fruit_tree_domestication_help_description">
Allows you to plant (b)fruit trees(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="rye_domestication_help_description">
Allows you to plant and harvest rye, increasing the crop variety is a good way to protect against (b)diseases(/b).
	</string>
		
	<string name="wheel_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Carts(/b) which will allow you to (b)transport(/b) a large amount of (b)resources(/b).
	</string>
	
 <!-- === Bronze Age === -->
 
	<string name="bronze_smelting_help_description">
Unlocks the production of (b)Bronze(/b) in (b)Pit Furnaces(/b) and the creation of (b)Bronze(/b) tools and weapons.
Unlocks the (b)Bronze Age(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="masonry_help_description">
Unlocks (b)Stone(/b) structures that are in general more (b)durable(/b) and advanced than (b)Mud(/b) structures.
	</string>
	
	<string name="swordmaking_help_description">
Unlocks (b)Swords(/b), which are the most (b)effective melee weapon(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="shieldmaking_help_description">
Unlocks (b)Shields(/b), which allow your people to block attacks.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="composite_archery_help_description">
Unlocks (b)Composite Bows(/b), which are the most effective (b)hunting weapon(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="brewing_help_description">
Unlocks the production of (b)Beer(/b), which can help boost (b)Morale(/b) in the settlement.
	</string>
	
	<string name="plowing_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Plows(/b) which will allow you to plant crops a lot more efficiently.
	</string>
	
 <!-- === Iron Age === -->
 
	<string name="iron_smelting_help_description">
Unlocks the smelting of (b)Iron(/b) in (b)Bloomeries(/b), the (b)Blacksmith(/b) structure and the creation of (b)Iron(/b) tools and weapons.
Unlocks the (b)Iron Age(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="steelmaking_help_description">
Unlocks the production of (b)Steel(/b), which is the (b)hardest(/b) and (b)most durable(/b) material available in ancient times.
	</string>
	
	<string name="hydropower_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Watermills(/b), which can greatly speed up the production of (b)Flour(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="baking_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of (b)Ovens(/b), which can greatly speed up the production of (b)Bread(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="staddle_stones_help_description">
Unlocks the construction of the (b)Staddle Granary(/b) structure, where you can store more food for longer.
	</string> 		

  <!-- === ANIMALS: categories === -->	
  
	<string name="help_domestic_animals_description">
Domestic animals provide a variety of benefits to your settlement: (b)protection(/b), (b)food(/b), (b)resources(/b) and (b)muscle power(/b).
You can obtain domestic animals by (b)purchasing(/b) them from traders, or by (b)domesticating young(/b) individuals of the equivalent wild variant.
Animals need to be sheltered in winter, and be provided with (b)Water(/b) and (b)Straw(/b). If there is no (b)Straw(/b) available, you can feed them with (b)Grain(/b).
Note that (b)Dogs(/b), as well as (b)Cattle(/b), (b)Donkeys(/b) or (b)Horses(/b) that are (b)attached to transports or Plows(/b), don't need shelter or food in winter.
Adult females will get pregnant and give (b)birth(/b) to new animals as long as there is an adult or old male around.
Note that your people will automatically (b)slaughter(/b) any domestic animals that are (b)too old(/b), even if they are below the limit.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_wild_animals_description">
Wild animals inhabit the land and for the most part (b)avoid humans(/b).
Predators will pose a threat if they are (b)very hungry(/b), or if they feel (b)threatened(/b).
	</string>
  
  <!-- === Animals === -->
  
	<string name="dog_help_description">
(b)Dogs(/b) are the first domestic animals to show up in your settlement. They are excellent (b)guards(/b) and will help you fight any intruders.
Once the (b)Dog Domestication(/b) tech is researched, dogs will keep on coming to the village at a steady rate, depending on your population.
They eat the leftovers from the humans, so they don't require to be fed or given shelter.
	</string>
	
	<string name="goat_help_description">
(b)Goats(/b) produce (b)Milk(/b) and can also be slaughtered to obtain (b)Meat(/b) and (b)Skins(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="sheep_help_description">
(b)Sheep(/b) produce (b)Wool(/b) and can also be slaughtered to obtain (b)Meat(/b) and (b)Skins(/b).
	</string>		
	
	<string name="pig_help_description">
(b)Pigs(/b) are primarily a source of (b)Meat(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="cattle_help_description">
(b)Cattle(/b) are a large domestic animal, that can be used to accomplish a variety of tasks.
They are the largest producer of (b)Milk(/b).
They can be slaughtered to obtain to obtain (b)Meat(/b) and (b)Skins(/b).
Additionally, (b)adults(/b) can also be used to pull plows, which greatly reduces the time it takes to plant crops.
They (b)consume more(/b) food and water in winter when compared to smaller animals like (b)Goats(/b) or (b)Sheep(/b).
	</string>		
	
	<string name="donkey_help_description">
(b)Donkeys(/b) are used primarily to pull (b)Carts(/b), but they can also be slaughtered to obtain (b)Meat(/b) and (b)Skins(/b).
Only (b)adult(/b) donkeys can work, so when you domesticate an animal from the wild, you need to wait for it to become an adult before it can be attached it to a cart.
	</string>

	<string name="horse_help_description">
(b)Horses(/b) are used primarily to pull (b)Carts(/b) and (b)Plows(/b), but they can also be slaughtered to obtain (b)Meat(/b) and (b)Skins(/b).
Only (b)adult(/b) horses can work, so when you domesticate an animal from the wild, you need to wait for it to become an adult before it can be attached it to a cart or plow.
	</string>			
	
	<string name="herbivore_help_description">
Herbivores roam the land and feed from grass. They are one of the primary sources of (b)Meat(/b), (b)Raw Skins(/b) and (b)Bones(/b).
Healthy (b)adults(/b) are faster and (b)tougher(/b), so they require better tools or more hunters to be dealt with effectively.
You can identify the easier prey using (b)primal vision(/b) or by clicking on individuals.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="large_herbivore_help_description">
Large herbivores will provide your people with large amounts of vital (b)resources(/b).
However they are used to defending themselves against predators, and (b)might retaliate(/b) if attacked. Approach them with care.
	</string>		
	
	<string name="predator_help_description">
Predators are animals that naturally prey on others. For the most part they will leave humans alone, unless hungry or provoked.
You can use (b)primal vision(/b) to identify them on the map, where they will show highlighted in orange or red.
	</string>

	<!-- === TRANSPORTS (no categories) === -->

	<string name="sledge_short_description">A basic human pulled transport</string>
	<string name="sledge_help_description">
The most basic form of transport, it allows one adult to move around (b)heavy resources(/b) with ease.
	</string>

	<string name="cart_short_description">A wheeled transport pulled by animals</string>
	<string name="cart_help_description">
Allows your people to move (b)large quantities(/b) of (b)heavy resources(/b) around.
Carts are pulled by (b)Donkeys(/b) or (b)Horses(/b). 
Only (b)adult(/b) animals can be used to pull carts.
When an animal is available, it will get attached to the transport automatically.
	</string>
	
	<string name="plow_short_description">A tool to prepare the fields to plant crops</string>
	<string name="plow_help_description">
An implement to prepare the fields to plant crops. 
Can be pulled by (b)Cattle(/b) or (b)Horses(/b).
Only (b)adult(/b) animals can be used to pull plows.
Allows your people to (b)plant(/b) crops much (b)faster(/b) and without a penalty to (b)morale(/b).
	</string>	
	
	<string name="rolling_megalith_short_description">A specialized transport to move megaliths</string>
	<string name="rolling_megalith_help_description">
To move (b)Megaliths(/b) around they are placed into rolling timbers, and then pulled by (b)several humans(/b).
	</string>

	<!-- === PLANTS === -->
	<string name="help_related_techs">Related Techs</string>

	<string name="help_plants_description">
Plants that grow in the wild are a great source of (b)resources(/b).
Once you have the appropriate (b)techs(/b), you will be able to (b)plant(/b) some of them yourself.
	</string>

	<string name="help_plant_harvesting_season">Harvesting Season</string>
	<string name="help_plant_planting_season">Planting Season</string>
	<string name="help_plant_disease_resistance">Disease Resistance: (1)%</string>
	<string name="help_plant_extra_production">(1)% chance of producing extra resource: (2)</string>

	<string name="help_plant_type_cereals">Cereals</string>
	<string name="help_plant_type_berries">Berries</string>
	<string name="help_plant_type_pulses">Pulses</string>
	<string name="help_plant_type_fruit_trees">Fruit Trees</string>
	<string name="help_plant_type_other">Other</string>
	
	<string name="help_einkorn_description">
A hardy cereal, (b)resistant(/b) against diseases.
	</string>

	<string name="help_emmer_description">
A high yield cereal, produces (b)extra Grain(/b).
	</string>

	<string name="help_barley_description">
A cereal that produces (b)extra Straw(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_flax_description">
A plant that produces (b)Linen(/b).
	</string>	

	<string name="help_peas_description">
A nutritious legume.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_chickpeas_description">
A nutritious legume.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_lentils_description">
A nutritious legume.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_bitter_vetch_description">
A nutritious legume.
It can grow wild, but it can also be planted.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_strawberry_description">
A wild collectable seasonal berry.
	</string>		
	
	<string name="help_blackberry_description">
A wild collectable seasonal berry.
	</string>		
	
	<string name="help_blueberry_description">
A wild collectable seasonal berry.
	</string>	
	
	<string name="help_raspberry_description">
A wild collectable seasonal berry.
	</string>			
	
	<string name="help_chestnut_description">
Produces nutritious chestnuts.
	</string>		
	
	<string name="help_pear_description">
Produces nutritious fruit.
	</string>			
	
	<string name="help_service_description">
Produces nutritious fruit.
	</string>		
	
	<string name="help_cherry_description">
Produces nutritious fruit.
	</string>			

	<string name="help_rye_description">
An all round cereal, more (b)resistant(/b) than most, and produces a good amount of (b)Grain(/b).
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_oak_description">
(b)Tannin(/b), an essential ingredient for the manufacturing of (b)Leather(/b) can be obtained from the bark of this tree.
	</string>	

	<string name="help_fir_description">
(b)Tannin(/b), an essential ingredient for the manufacturing of (b)Leather(/b) can be obtained from the bark of this tree.
	</string>	
	
	
</strings>